buzzen.com 2008-12-16

# Online Chat Rooms at Buzzen - Free chat - Live chat - Chat Now! Find New Friends at Buzzen Chat!

Chat Code of Conduct  
SpaceDom Code of Conduct  
Buzzen Supported Room Code of Conduct  
Terms of Use

Privacy Statement

**COPYRIGHT© 2004 - THIS YEAR BUZZEN COMMUNICATIONS INC:**

The contents of this website is copyrighted © 2004-THIS YEAR BUZZEN COMMUNICATIONS INC. All rights reserved. This website is for personal use only and not to be used in any commercial manner. You are strictly prohibited from using any graphics, designs, information etc. for your own personal use on any other website without prior written consent from Buzzen Executive. 

**Your Personal Information:**

Buzzen understands that your personal information is very important to you, and that you have a right not to disclose such information. By providing personal information to Buzzen, we know you do so in the utmost trust and so will guarantee that your personal information stays private.

**Buzzen Membership**

By becomming a member of Buzzen, you are provided with a great deal more access to features, inaccessible to guests or non-members. The benefits of being a member include, but are not limited to: the use of interactive tools, such as email, chat, gaming and 24 hour technical assistance. To keep you up to date with network updates and changes you may also recieve newsletters.

**Collected Information:**

There are two (2) ways in which Buzzen may collect information from or about you.

1) If you login as a member - we have obtained a rough idea of your geographical location, which which we use to further develop our database to determine high-traffic areas. 

2) If you visit our network as a non-member or visitor - we deterime what you like to see, and what you like to look at to further improve our services to both members and guests. If you do not register with our network; all your information remains anonymous.

**Preserving Your Privacy**

We understand that some do not like disclosing personal information to become a member. If you would rather not provide your real name you can provide us with a pseudonym (or "nym") - a different name. This name is what you will be known as and also referred to as by staff. We won't know who you are.

**Using Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information which are transfered to your computer hard drive for recording purposes. Most web browsers will accept cookies, however if you wish you can chose not to accept any cookies. This may cause some pages not to work to the fullest potential and decrease your overall experience of certain services.

The use of cookies can overall enhance your experience, as we're able to create the services you like to suit you more. These cookies can also assist in understanding which advertisments are effective.

**The use of cookies can help determine:**

  * The number of page views.
  * The number of unique visitors.
  * How long such visitors spend on the network.
  * Most frequented webpages.

**Using & Disclosing your information:**

Your information will not be disclosed to anyone without your consent, with exception to:

  * the demand of law enforcement agencies. (State, National & International)
  * We suspect that your use of the network is in violation of this document and the code of conduct.
  * To protect the rights of Buzzen Communications Inc. It's members and guests.
  * To lessen a serious threat to a persons health or safety.

Buzzen will not share your personal information to any third party clientel.

**Storing & Keeping your information secure:**

We will make EVERY effort to prevent the disclosure of your information to any third party clientel or other user. As services grow we will further increase our network's security.

Our employees are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any information supplied to us and held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. 

You can also assist in protecting your personal information by contacting your local technician or computer shop on ways to protect your computer and by informing Buzzen if there is any unauthorized access to your account.

**Problems & Questions:**

Should be raised by emailing: [privacy@buzzen.com](mailto:privacy@buzzen.com)

**Changes to the Privacy Statement:**

Buzzen Communications Incorporation reserves the right to update it's privacy statement without notice. We encourage you to review the statement regularly as updates are made with the addition of new features.
